Inventory of the Constantine Peter Arnold papers, 1841-1943
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Constantine Peter Arnold papers
1841-1943
Arnold, Constantine Peter, 1860-1943.
00002
circa 22 cubic feet (49 boxes)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Biography of Constantine Peter Arnold
C.P. Arnold was an early resident of Laramie, Wyoming. He was a lawyer, Democratic politician and businessman and the father of Thurman Arnold (Pres. Roosevelt's well-known trust buster).
Scope and Content
The collection contains 17 boxes of legal case folders, 5 boxes of legal documents and 3 boxes of manuscripts, speeches and original poetry. The collection also contains 7 boxes of correspondence (1841-1943) and 1 box of maps, and blueprints and scrapbooks, photographs and printed material. There are also 20 financial ledgers and account books which preserve records of Arnold's business interests.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Constantine Peter Arnold at the date of processing.
Additional Information
Finding aid available in repository.
Acquisition Information
The collection was received from C.P. Arnold in 1945 and by Wilson Clough and an unknown donor, 1959-1962. Material was also received from Alice Moudy Robbins in 1975.
Access Terms
Arnold, Thurman Wesley, 1891-1969.; Arnold family.; Oasis Land and Cattle Company.; Millbrook Land and Livestock Company.; Cattle trade -- Wyoming.; Laramie (Wyo.); Albany County (Wyo.); Maps.; Blueprints.; Scrapbooks.; Photographs.; Ledgers.; Lawyers.
Ranching; Wyoming
Container List
- Series I. Books, Essays, Manuscripts, and Poetry
  - Books
    - Aven Nelson, Analytical Key of Some of the Common Flowering Plants of the Rocky Mountain Region, undated (Box 45)
    - F. R. Marshall, Breeding Farm Animals, undated (Box 45)
    - George A. Martin, Farm Appliances, undated (Box 45)
    - William Miles, Horse’s Foot, and How to Keep It Sound, undated (Box 45)
    - John Stuart Mill, On Liberty, the Subjection of Women, undated (Box 45)
    - Jas Miller, Our Excellent Women of the Methodist Church, in England and America, undated (Box 45)
    - T. L. Miller, History of Hereford Cattle, undated (Box 45)
    - C. E. Page, Horses: Their Feed and Their Feet, undated (Box 45)
    - Pastoralist’s Review, Stockowner’s Guide, undated (Box 45)
    - Jacob Harris Patton, Patton’s Concise History of the American People, undated (Box 45)
    - George E. Rich, Artistic Horse-Shoeing, undated (Box 45)
    - Roma, Geographical Review, undated (Box 45)
    - William A. Rushworth (Dr.), Sheep and Their Diseases, undated (Box 45)
    - George Frederick Ruxton, In the Old West, undated (Box 45)
    - Henry Stewart, Domestic Sheep, Its Culture and General Management, undated (Box 45)
  - Essays
    - Another Lawsuit, undated (Box 45)
    - Introduction to Literature West of the Missouri River, undated (Box 45)
    - Should you Care to Know, undated (Box 45)
    - Thomas Paine, undated (Box 45)
    - Western Tales for Cyclone Cellars, undated (Box 45)
  - Manuscripts
    - A By-Gone Type of Iowa Litigation (2), undated (Box 34)
    - A Colonial Graveyard (5), undated (Box 34)
    - A Free Man’s Worship, undated (Box 34)
    - A Modern Parable, undated (Box 34)
    - A Sleeping Volcano, undated (Box 35)
    - Address of Welcome (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Another Lawsuit, undated (Box 34)
    - Apprenticeship Continued, undated (Box 34)
    - Arrows in a Quiver, undated (Box 34)
    - By-Gone Types on Vanished Frontiers (3), undated (Box 34)
    - Cadets, undated (Box 34)
    - Camp Lewis (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Campaigning with Kennick (4), undated (Box 34)
    - The Center of Calm, undated (Box 34)
    - China to 600 A. D., undated (Box 34)
    - Christianity in History, undated (Box 34)
    - The Compensations of Life, undated (Box 34)
    - The Consolation of Life, undated (Box 34)
    - Criticism of Arnold S. Poems, undated (Box 34)
    - Don Quixote, undated (Box 34)
    - Early Ohio (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Easter, undated (Box 34)
    - Editorial Comment, undated (Box 34)
    - False Fronts, undated (Box 34)
    - Father and Son’s Week, undated (Box 34)
    - The Fossil Forest (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Getting an Education (2), undated (Box 34)
    - The Golden Harp, undated (Box 34)
    - The Great Victory (2), undated (Box 34)
    - The Greatest Human Document (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Haec Fabula Docet (3), undated (Box 34)
    - The Haunted Cabin at the Abandoned Mine (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Her Name I Do Not Know (3), undated (Box 34)
    - The Hospitality of the Scientific Mind (4), undated (Box 34)
    - The Indebtedness of Art to Christianity, undated (Box 34)
    - The Influence of the American Home, undated (Box 34)
    - In Re Barney-Haley, undated (Box 34)
    - Keeping the Road (3), undated (Box 34)
    - Knox, John - The Reformer, undated (Box 34)
    - The Ladder Man Climbed, undated (Box 34)
    - The Last of the Three Hundred Thousand, undated (Box 34)
    - Lincoln (2), undated (Box 34)
    - The Lover of Nature, undated (Box 34)
    - The Mayo Clinic, a Social Study, undated (Box 34)
    - Memorial Day Sermon, undated (Box 34)
    - Memorial Remarks on Justice Lurton, undated (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous (2), undated (Box 35)
    - My First Law Suit, undated (Box 34)
    - Naming the Post Office, undated (Box 34)
    - The Naming of Bate’s Hole, undated (Box 34)
    - Naming the Post Office, Nightingales Sing When Bombs Explode, undated (Box 34)
    - The New Contact of Science with the Man on the Street (2), undated (Box 34)
    - Nomenclature on the Frontier, undated (Box 34)
    - Nominating Address, undated (Box 34)
    - Old Denmark Days, undated (Box 35)
    - The Old Fashion College (2), undated (Box 35)
    - Old Wabash (5), undated (Box 35)
    - Ol’ Man River (2), undated (Box 35)
    - One of the Canterbury Pilgrims, Modern Version, undated (Box 35)
    - Past and Present, undated (Box 35)
    - Perfect Love Casteth Out Fear, undated (Box 35)
    - Poetic Paleobalany, undated (Box 35)
    - The Relation of the Church to the Community, undated (Box 35)
    - Remedial Legislation for Women, undated (Box 35)
    - Reservoirs, undated (Box 35)
    - Robinson (Senator), J. T., undated (Box 35)
    - See Wyoming, undated (Box 35)
    - Shattered, undated (Box 35)
    - Should You Care to Know (2), undated (Box 35)
    - Stage Coach Days, undated (Box 35)
    - Talks About Books, undated (Box 35)
    - The Tale of Two Centuries (3), undated (Box 35)
    - Taxation, undated (Box 35)
    - The Trees, undated (Box 35)
    - The Yucca and the Moth, undated (Box 35)
    - Vacation Hollidays, undated (Box 35)
    - Washington Irving, undated (Box 35)
    - Washington Irving and His Stories of the West, undated (Box 35)
    - Washington Irving’s Life of Mahomet, undated (Box 35)
    - West of the Missouri River (2), undated (Box 35)
    - Western Tales for Cyclone Cellars (5), undated (Box 35)
    - Westminster Abbey, undated (Box 35)
    - Who’s to Blame, undated (Box 35)
    - Writing Poetry, undated (Box 35)
    - Wyoming, undated (Box 35)
    - Wyoming Pioneer Association, undated (Box 35)
    - X Equals X, undated (Box 35)
  - Poetry
    - A Christmas Token, undated (Box 45)
    - Literature West of the Missouri River, undated (Box 45)
    - The Mayo Clinic: A Social Study, undated (Box 45)
    - The Pinion Pine, undated (Box 45)
- Series II. Case Folders
  - Acme Cement Plaster Co. - Suit, undated (Box 8)
  - Actions - Based on Ownership or Possession, undated (Box 8)
  - Advise Possession - 11 pages 150-160, undated (Box 8)
  - Affectation with Public Interest, undated (Box 8)
  - Air Pages 11-33, undated (Box 8)
  - Alien Custodian 133, undated (Box 8)
  - Arnold, C. P., undated (Box 8)
  - Arnold, C. P. - vs. Federal Land Bank, undated (Box 8)
  - Arnold, C. P. - Papers and Correspondence 135, undated (Box 8)
  - Assignments of oil and Gas Leases, undated (Box 8)
  - Bridges vs. Woolf No. 222, undated (Box 9)
  - Burleson, Dr. Willard - Grand Rapids, Michigan, undated (Box 9)
  - Caldwell and Cameron vs. McDowell, Mrs. Anna J. No. 89, undated (Box 10)
  - Caldwell vs. Matson (2 Folders), undated (Box 10)
  - Caldwell vs. Matson, Ed. No. 284, undated (Box 10)
  - Cameron vs. State Bank, undated (Box 10)
  - Central Drub vs. Converse No. 177A, undated (Box 10)
  - Certain - Teed Products Corp., undated (Box 10)
  - Chicos vs. Kolin No. 226A, undated (Box 10)
  - Christian Elsie Estate, undated (Box 10)
  - City Bank and Trust Co., Denver. Joe Lane No. 70, undated (Box 10)
  - Commencement Address, undated (Box 10)
  - Constitutional Law, undated (Box 10)
  - Constitutional Law - Function of Judiciary in Enforcing Constitutions, undated (Box 10)
  - Cresent Mercantile Co. No. 239, undated (Box 10)
  - Cumming, D. W. Applications, undated (Box 10)
  - Decker, et al No. 71, undated (Box 11)
  - Dieu vs. Gibhardt No. 141, undated (Box 11)
  - Discher vs. Brandenburg, undated (Box 11)
  - Downey and Tidball, Judge V. J. No. 60, undated (Box 11)
  - Due Process - Equal Protection - Section I, undated (Box 11)
  - Due Process - Equal Protection II Classification, undated (Box 11)
  - Easements By Implications, undated (Box 11)
  - Ejectment - Oil and Gas, undated (Box 11)
  - Engen vs. Rambler Cooper Co. No. 140, undated (Box 11)
  - Ernest Bros, vs. Cresent Mercantile Co. No. 239, undated (Box 11)
  - Ernest vs. Ernest No. 130, undated (Box 11)
  - Eykyn, Geo R., undated (Box 11)
  - Featherstone County Case No. 114, undated (Box 11)
  - First Trust and Savings Bank vs. Patterson No. 177, undated (Box 11)
  - Fisher, E. E. vs. Weber Chimney Co. No. 204, undated (Box 11)
  - Fixtures, undated (Box 11)
  - Ford, C. W. vs. Tie State Oil Co. No. 145, undated (Box 11)
  - Forfeiture - Oil and Gas Leases, undated (Box 11)
  - Fort Collins Contract - Alkali Dome, Carpenter’s App., undated (Box 11)
  - Galbraith, Henry - Estate of No. 15, undated (Box 12)
  - Gardner, Robert - In the Matter of Estate of No. 16, undated (Box 12)
  - German Consulate - Seattle No. 42, undated (Box 12)
  - Gift, undated (Box 12)
  - Gilbert, Ernest 194, undated (Box 12)
  - Grable and Bell Land Papers, undated (Box 12)
  - Grand View Addition No. 122, undated (Box 12)
  - Griffey, Tol No. 219A, undated (Box 12)
  - Grover Well Case No. 72, undated (Box 12)
  - Habendum, Clause - Duration of Lease, undated (Box 13)
  - Haley, Ora, undated (Box 13)
  - Haley, Ora Estate of, undated (Box 13)
  - Hamby vs. Woodhouse No. 200, undated (Box 13)
  - Hanna vs. Glads, undated (Box 13)
  - Hart and Co. No. 234, undated (Box 13)
  - Hartman, Ed. No. 73, undated (Box 13)
  - Haynes, H. N. No. 74, undated (Box 13)
  - Herrick File, undated (Box 13)
  - Hodgman et al vs. Baird no. 75, undated (Box 13)
  - Holliday, W. H. Accounts No. 129, undated (Box 13)
  - Hooker vs. Hooker No. 250, undated (Box 13)
  - Hoss - Patterson Co., undated (Box 13)
  - Hunt, Ed. vs. Lewis Butler No. 218, undated (Box 13)
  - Ihmsen vs. Fred F. Banforth, undated (Box 14)
  - Insurance Notes, undated (Box 14)
  - Interstate Reservoirs Con Co., undated (Box 14)
  - Interstate Union National Bank - Greeley, undated (Box 14)
  - Judgment and Satisfaction of Judgment, undated (Box 14)
  - Kassahn vs. Young no. 175, undated (Box 14)
  - King vs. King - Divorce No. 76, undated (Box 14)
  - King vs. King - Letters No. 77, undated (Box 14)
  - King vs. Laughlin No. 78, undated (Box 14)
  - Kinney - Dallas Live Stock Co., undated (Box 14)
  - Knudsen, Dallas and Hoss, undated (Box 14)
  - La Pash and Converse No. 143, undated (Box 15)
  - La Paz Oil Co. - J. M. Hodgson - Lost Soldier Development Co. No. 231, undated (Box 15)
  - Law School Notice, undated (Box 14)
  - Legal Bibliography, undated (Box 15)
  - Liberty of Contract, undated (Box 15)
  - Library, undated (Box 15)
  - Mahs, Bertha - Estate of No. 205, undated (Box 15)
  - Manitowoc Shipbuilding Corp. vs. Johnson No. 275, undated (Box 15)
  - Marketing Act, undated (Box 15)
  - Markley vs. Sodergreen No. 131, undated (Box 15)
  - Marlow vs. Cameron No. 119, undated (Box 15)
  - Martin, Kate no. 117, undated (Box 15)
  - Mathison Case No. 79, undated (Box 15)
  - Maud, undated (Box 15)
  - Maynard vs. Laramie No. 240, undated (Box 15)
  - McDonald Livestock Co. No. 81, undated (Box 15)
  - McMurtrie No. 118, undated (Box 15)
  - Merrill Appeal No. 33, undated (Box 15)
  - Michaels, F. A., undated (Box 15)
  - Millbrook Land and Live Stock Co. - Foreclosure Papers No.44, undated (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous - “R” No. 98, undated (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous - “W” No. 97, undated (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous - Correspondence, undated (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous No. 142, undated (Box 16)
  - Montgomery Estate No. 80, undated (Box 16)
  - Mortgages, undated (Box 16)
  - Moudy Alice (Town Property) Deeds, etc., undated (Box 16)
  - Moudy, Alice Maud No. 257, undated (Box 16)
  - Municipal Contracting Co., undated (Box 16)
  - Nature of Landowner’s Right in Oil and Gas, undated (Box 17)
  - Nature of Lease’s Interest, undated (Box 17)
  - Nerheim vs. Schmitzler, undated (Box 17)
  - Nesheim vs. Holliday Co. No. 173, undated (Box 17)
  - Notes on Partnership, undated (Box 17)
  - Oil Rights in Public Lands, undated (Box 17)
  - Operation of 14th Amendment, undated (Box 17)
  - Otterson, Otto No. 99, undated (Box 17)
  - Palmer, Axel No. 241, undated (Box 18)
  - Paulson, No. 107, undated (Box 18)
  - Peabody Estate No. 241, undated (Box 18)
  - Personal - Seconds, undated (Box 18)
  - Philbrick, Mable, undated (Box 18)
  - Possession Pages 1-9 Chapter I, Rights Irrelevant to Possession, undated (Box 18)
  - Powell, Von vs. Kasoming Oil No. 178, undated (Box 18)
  - Price, Dr. J. W. No. 209, undated (Box 18)
  - Privileges and Immunities, undated (Box 18)
  - Puis Estate - Recent Correspondence No. 110, undated (Box 18)
  - Real Property Problems, undated (Box 19)
  - Reid Ranch - Current Accounts No. 109, undated (Box 19)
  - Reid Ranch Fire No. 111, undated (Box 19)
  - Rents and Royalties, undated (Box 19)
  - Retirement System - Corr., undated (Box 19)
  - Rexford vs. Grounds, undated (Box 19)
  - Roach Papers, Guarantee Trust Co. Sodergreen Case No.47, undated (Box 19)
  - Rock Creek Coal Co. No. 225, undated (Box 19)
  - Rock Creek Coal Co. No. 226, undated (Box 19)
  - Rock Creek Coal Co. vs. Maynard No. 241, undated (Box 19)
  - Salt Creek Syndicate No. 197, undated (Box 19)
  - Sawyer, C. J. No. 263, undated (Box 19)
  - School Mandamus No. 198, undated (Box 19)
  - Scoville Live Stock Co., undated (Box 19)
  - Section 2 III Pledge, undated (Box 19)
  - Singer Estate, undated (Box 19)
  - Smith Vs. Donahue No. 222A, undated (Box 19)
  - Spaulding vs. Denver-Laramie, undated (Box 19)
  - Spaulding, P. W. No. 106, undated (Box 19)
  - Springbrook Land Co. - vs. Akin, Arthur et al, undated (Box 19)
  - Stewart, Charles No. 182, undated (Box 20)
  - Stockman's state Bank of Medicine Bow vs. Bennett Estate, undated (Box 20)
  - Stockman’s State Bank of Medicine Bow vs. Bennett, Ralph L. (2 Folders), undated (Box 20)
  - Stockman’s State Bank vs. Atkinson No. 265, undated (Box 20)
  - Stoddard vs. Royal Insurance Co. No. 88, undated (Box 20)
  - Sullivan vs. first National Bank of Rock River No. 219, undated (Box 20)
  - Sullivan vs. Rock River St. Bank No. 217, undated (Box 20)
  - Tallmadge, E. R. Chicago, III. no. 91, undated (Box 21)
  - Taxation, undated (Box 21)
  - Taylor, R. S., Casper, Wyoming No. 126, undated (Box 21)
  - Termination I Abandonment, undated (Box 21)
  - Thomas Vs. Harden No. 252, undated (Box 21)
  - Thornton Case No. 90, undated (Box 21)
  - Union Pacific No. 115, undated (Box 21)
  - Union Pacific R. R. Co. Omaha, Nebraska, undated (Box 21)
  - United Shoe Co. vs. Anderson No. 251, undated (Box 21)
  - University of Wyoming No. 138, undated (Box 21)
  - Warren vs. Warren No. 195, undated (Box 22)
  - Water, undated (Box 22)
  - Water Restatements, undated (Box 22)
  - Watt, John No. 176, undated (Box 22)
  - Wheelock, Jesse M. and Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance, undated (Box 22)
  - Whitesides Deal, undated (Box 22)
  - Wilde vs. Federal Land Bank, undated (Box 22)
  - Wyoming Presses Brick Co. No. 201, undated (Box 22)
  - Wyoming Trout Co. vs. Denver-Laramie Realty Co. No. 94, undated (Box 22)
  - Yerxa vs. Harper, undated (Box 22)
  - Zuhlke, W. C. No. 224, undated (Box 22)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - 1908 January-December (Box 1)
  - 1909 January-December (Box 2)
  - 1910 (Box 2)
  - 1911 (Box 2)
  - 1912 January-December (Box 3)
  - 1913 January-December (Box 3)
  - 1914-1916 (Box 4)
  - 1917 January-December (Box 5)
  - 1918-1924 (Box 5)
  - 1925-1937 (Box 6)
  - 1938-1943 (Box 7)
  - 1898-1907 (Box 1)
  - -? to C. P. Arnold, 1943 March 10 (Box 45)
  - C. P. Arnold to Dr. Ruth A. Nelson, 1940 January 14 (Box 45)
  - C. P. Arnold to Maud Moudy, 1937 December 30 (Box 45)
  - C. P. Arnold to Maud Moudy, 1940 March 27 (Box 45)
  - C. P. Arnold to Maud Moudy, 1940 November 9 (Box 45)
  - C. P. Arnold to Maud Moudy, 1941 March 1 (Box 45)
  - C. P. Arnold to Wendell Wilkie, 1935 August 20 (Box 45)
  - C. P.Arnold to Dr. Seward, 1935 September 2 (Box 45)
  - C.P. Arnold to Maud Moudy, 1937 January 13 (Box 45)
  - C.P. Arnold to Maud Moudy, 1940 July 17 (Box 45)
  - Carl F. Arnold to C. P. Arnold, undated (Box 45)
  - Confederate Soldier to Jen -?, undated (Box 45)
  - Edman Powel to Elizabeth Fall, 1841 July 26 (Box 45)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt to Thurman W. Arnold, 1943 January 8 (Box 45)
  - Prestin Slosson to -?, 1939 January 14-February 12 (Box 45)
  - Santa Claus to Maud Moudy, 1884 December 25 (Box 45)
  - Sarah -? to Mrs. Brockway, 1850 October 9 (Box 45)
  - Thurman W. Arnold to C. P. Arnold, 1937 December 21 (Box 45)
  - Thurman W. Arnold to C. P. Arnold, undated (Box 45)
  - Thurman W. Arnold to C. P. Arnold, undated (Box 45)
  - W. E. Chaplin to Alice Maude Moudy, 1900 February 23 (Box 45)
  - Wendell Wilkie to C. P. Arnold, 1935 August 23 (Box 45)
- Series IV. Financial Files
  - Ledger Books
    - No. 1: Ledger, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 2: Oasis Land and Cattle Company or Wyoming, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 3: Cash and Bank Accounts, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 4: Harold Doke Account, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 5: C. P. Arnold’s Accounts, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 6: List of Article Purchased, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 7: Daily Statement Book, undated (Box 46)
    - No. 8: C. P. Arnold Accounts, undated (Box 47)
    - No. 9: Cash Book, undated (Box 47)
    - No. 10: Office Docket, undated (Box 47)
    - No. 11: Incoming Accounting Record, undated (Box 47)
    - No. 12: Incoming Accounting Record, undated (Box 47)
    - No. 13: Accounts of Hart and Co., undated (Box 47)
    - No. 14: Journal, undated (Box 47)
    - No. 15: Millbrook Land and Livestock Co., undated (Box 47)
    - No. 16: Ledger of Accounts, undated (Box 48)
    - No. 17: Receipt Book, undated (Box 48)
    - No. 18: Day Book, undated (Box 48)
    - No. 19: Record of Minutes - Cosgriff and Fuller, undated (Box 48)
    - No. 20: First National Bank Ledger, undated (Box 48)
- Series V. General Material
  - Abstracts of Title, undated (Box 28)
  - Acme Plaster, undated (Box 28)
  - Adjudication, undated (Box 29)
  - Bank Statements, undated (Box 30)
  - Bills, undated (Box 31)
  - Campaign Relies, undated (Box 31)
  - Cuts, undated (Box 31)
  - Deer, undated (Box 31)
  - Descriptions (Land), undated (Box 32)
  - Devil’s Tower, undated (Box 31)
  - Envelopes (Empty), undated (Box 32)
  - Federal Land Bank Files, undated (Box 32)
  - Green River Lake Sublette County, undated (Box 31)
  - Insurance Papers, undated (Box 33)
  - Land Office Decision Blanks, undated (Box 33)
  - Pioneers - J. M. Abney and F. C. Burnett, undated (Box 31)
  - Pioneers - Pioneer Cabin, Douglas, undated (Box 31)
  - Plays, undated (Box 40)
  - Poems, undated (Box 40)
  - Receipts, undated (Box 41)
  - Scrapbooks (4), undated (Box 42)
  - Taxes, undated (Box 43)
  - Taxes, undated (Box 44)
  - Tetons, undated (Box 31)
- Series VI. Legal Files
  - Abstract of Title (3), undated (Box 23)
  - Account of Disbursements, undated (Box 23)
  - Adjudication of Priorities - Water, undated (Box 23)
  - Adjustment of Taxes Paid, undated (Box 23)
  - Administratrix’ Deed (2), undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavit for Interpleader, undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavit in Renewal of Chattel Mortgage, undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavit of Loss, undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavit of Publication, undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavit of Rebate of Taxes, undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavit of the President and Secretary, etc, undated (Box 23)
  - Affidavits (37), undated (Box 23)
  - Agreements (24), undated (Box 23)
  - Agreements (Memorandum Of) (19), undated (Box 23)
  - Amended and Supplemental Petition, undated (Box 23)
  - Amended Application for Prospecting Permit, undated (Box 23)
  - Amended Petition (2), undated (Box 23)
  - Analysis of Amended Petition, undated (Box 24)
  - Answer (3), undated (Box 24)
  - Application for a Permit to Appropriate the Water of the State of Wyoming, undated (Box 24)
  - Application for Permit to Prospect for Oil and Gas, undated (Box 24)
  - Application for Probate of Foreign Will, undated (Box 24)
  - Application for Prospecting Permit (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Application of Judgment on Default, undated (Box 24)
  - Application of Scoville Live Stock Company, undated (Box 24)
  - Applications (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Applications for Attorney’s Fees (5), undated (Box 24)
  - Appointment of Commissioners, undated (Box 24)
  - Arnold’s Testimony, undated (Box 24)
  - Articles of Incorporation - Laramie Development Co., undated (Box 24)
  - Articles of Incorporation - Little Powder Live Stock Co. (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Articles of Incorporation - McDonald Live Stock Co. (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Articles of Incorporation - Scoville Live Stock Co. (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Assignment (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Assignment of Contract, undated (Box 24)
  - Assignment of Policy (5), undated (Box 24)
  - Bill, undated (Box 24)
  - Bill of Complaint, undated (Box 24)
  - Bill of Sale (3), undated (Box 24)
  - Bond Applications, undated (Box 24)
  - Brief, undated (Box 24)
  - Brief for Davis and Thomas, etc., undated (Box 24)
  - Brief on Question of Redemption (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Caption Sheet, undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate (3), undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate of Acknowledgment of Execution of Documents (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate of Appropriation of Water (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate of Award of Commissioners, undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate of Consolidation of the Rock River State Bank with the First National Bank of Rock River, undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate of Incorporation of the Interstate Reservoir, undated (Box 24)
  - Certificate of Redemption, undated (Box 24)
  - Chattel Mortgage, undated (Box 24)
  - Consent Decree, undated (Box 24)
  - Consent Judgment, undated (Box 24)
  - Decree, undated (Box 24)
  - Decree of Court (5), undated (Box 24)
  - Decree of Final Distribution (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Deed of Administrator, undated (Box 24)
  - Deeds (3), undated (Box 24)
  - Demand, undated (Box 24)
  - Deposition (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Description of Land (4), undated (Box 24)
  - Discharge, undated (Box 24)
  - Election of Secretary-Treasurer, undated (Box 24)
  - Exhibits (2), undated (Box 24)
  - Final Order Vesting Title in the United states of America, undated (Box 24)
  - Findings and Judgment (7), undated (Box 24)
  - Guardian’s Deed, undated (Box 24)
  - Herrick Suit, undated (Box 24)
  - Indemnity Bond, undated (Box 24)
  - Indentures (4), undated (Box 24)
  - Insurance Papers (4), undated (Box 24)